<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">Women Empowerment</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Benefits of women empowerment</string>
    <string name="artical_text">Women empowerment adds to confidence of women in their ability to lead meaningful and purposeful lives. It removes their dependence on others and makes them individuals in their own right.
\n\n
They are able to lead their lives with dignity and freedom
\nIt adds to their self esteem
\nIt gives them a distinct identity
\nThey are able to gain positions of respect in society
As they are financially independent they are able to spend on all their needs and desires
They are able to make meaningful contributions to the well-being of society
They act as capable citizens to make the country achieve enhanced Gross Domestic Product (GDP) growth
They get fair and equitable access to resources of the country
Necessity of Women\’s Empowerment

Without women\’s empowerment, we cannot remove injustice and gen  www.indiacelebrating.com/article/article-on-women-empowerment/ Women empowerment has become the buzzword today with women working alongside men in all spheres. They profess an independent outlook, whether they are living inside their home or working outside. They are increasingly gaining control over their lives and taking their own decisions with regard to their education, career, profession and lifestyle.
\n\n
    With steady increase in the number of working women, they have gained financial independence, which has given them confidence to lead their own lives and build their own identity. They are successfully taking up diverse professions to prove that they are second to none in any respect.
\n\n
    But while doing so, women also take care to strike a balance between their commitment to their profession as well as their home and family. They are playing multiple roles of a mother, daughter, sister, wife and a working professional with remarkable harmony and ease.With equal opportunities to work, they are functioning with a spirit of team work to render all possible co-operation to their male counterparts in meeting the deadlines and targets set in their respective professions.
\n\n
        Women empowerment is not limited to urban, working women but women in even remote towns and villages are now increasingly making their voices heard loud. </string>
</resources>
